{"problemsArray": [
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 4)(3x + 2)/(3x + 5)(3x + 5)"], "answer": "(9x^2 + 18x + 8)/(9x^2 + 30x + 25)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 4)(3x + 2)/(3x + 5)(3x + 5)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 4)/(3x + 5) * (3x + 2)/(3x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 4)(3x + 2)/(3x + 5)(3x + 5)"], "answer": "(3x + 4)/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(2x + 5)/(3x + 1)*(3x + 4)/(2x + 5)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 5)(3x + 4)/(3x + 1)(2x + 5)\n\n2x + 5 cancels out, so we get (3x + 4)/(3x + 1) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 5)/(3x + 1) / (2x + 5)/(3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 4)(3x + 2)/(3x + 5)(3x + 5)"], "answer": "(2x + 1)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 2)(2x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get (2x + 1)/(2x + 5) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 2)/(2x + 5) * (2x + 1)/(3x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 4)(3x + 2)/(3x + 5)(3x + 5)"], "answer": "(2x + 5)/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 3)(2x + 5)/(3x + 1)(2x + 3)\n\n2x + 3 cancels out, so we get (2x + 5)/(3x + 1) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 3)/(3x + 1) * (2x + 5)/(2x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 4)(3x + 2)/(3x + 5)(3x + 5)"], "answer": "(3x + 2)/(2x + 3)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 2)/(3x + 5) * (3x + 5)/(2x + 3)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 2)(3x + 5)/(3x + 5)(2x + 3)\n\n3x + 5 cancels out, so we get (3x + 2)/(2x + 3) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 2)/(3x + 5) / (2x + 3)/(3x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 5)/(3x + 2)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(6x^2 + 13x + 5)/(9x^2 + 9x + 2)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 1)(3x + 5)/(3x + 2)(3x + 1)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 1)/(3x + 2) * (3x + 5)/(3x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 5)/(3x + 2)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(3x + 4)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 4)/(3x + 2) * (3x + 2)/(2x + 5)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 4)(3x + 2)/(3x + 2)(2x + 5)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get (3x + 4)/(2x + 5) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 4)/(3x + 2) / (2x + 5)/(3x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 5)/(3x + 2)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(2x + 1)/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(2x + 1)/(3x + 1)*(2x + 1)/(2x + 1)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 1)(2x + 1)/(3x + 1)(2x + 1)\n\n2x + 1 cancels out, so we get (2x + 1)/(3x + 1) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 1)/(3x + 1) / (2x + 1)/(2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 4)(2x + 5)/(3x + 5)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(6x^2 + 23x + 20)/(9x^2 + 18x + 5)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 4)(2x + 5)/(3x + 5)(3x + 1)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 4)/(3x + 5) * (2x + 5)/(3x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 4)(2x + 5)/(3x + 5)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(2x + 3)/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 3)(3x + 1)/(3x + 1)(2x + 1)\n\n3x + 1 cancels out, so we get (2x + 3)/(2x + 1) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 3)/(3x + 1) * (3x + 1)/(2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 2)(2x + 5)/(2x + 1)(2x + 1)"], "answer": "(6x^2 + 19x + 10)/(4x^2 + 4x + 1)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 2)(2x + 5)/(2x + 1)(2x + 1)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 2)/(2x + 1) * (2x + 5)/(2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 2)(2x + 5)/(2x + 1)(2x + 1)"], "answer": "(2x + 5)/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 2)/(2x + 1)*(2x + 5)/(3x + 2)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 2)(2x + 5)/(2x + 1)(3x + 2)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get (2x + 5)/(2x + 1) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 2)/(2x + 1) / (3x + 2)/(2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 2)(2x + 5)/(2x + 1)(2x + 1)"], "answer": "(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 1)/(3x + 4)*(2x + 1)/(3x + 1)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 1)(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)(3x + 1)\n\n3x + 1 cancels out, so we get (2x + 1)/(3x + 4) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 1)/(3x + 4) / (3x + 1)/(2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 2)(2x + 5)/(2x + 1)(2x + 1)"], "answer": "(2x + 3)/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 5)(2x + 3)/(2x + 1)(3x + 5)\n\n3x + 5 cancels out, so we get (2x + 3)/(2x + 1) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 5)/(2x + 1) * (2x + 3)/(3x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(2x + 3)/(3x + 4)(3x + 2)"], "answer": "(6x^2 + 11x + 3)/(9x^2 + 18x + 8)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 1)/(3x + 4) * (2x + 3)/(3x + 2)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 1)(2x + 3)/(3x + 4)(3x + 2)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 1)/(3x + 4) / (3x + 2)/(2x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(2x + 3)/(3x + 4)(3x + 2)"], "answer": "(2x + 5)/(3x + 2)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 4)(2x + 5)/(3x + 2)(3x + 4)\n\n3x + 4 cancels out, so we get (2x + 5)/(3x + 2) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 4)/(3x + 2) * (2x + 5)/(3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 4)(2x + 3)/(3x + 5)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(6x^2 + 17x + 12)/(9x^2 + 18x + 5)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 4)(2x + 3)/(3x + 5)(3x + 1)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 4)/(3x + 5) * (2x + 3)/(3x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 4)(2x + 3)/(3x + 5)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(3x + 1)/(3x + 2)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 5)(3x + 1)/(3x + 2)(2x + 5)\n\n2x + 5 cancels out, so we get (3x + 1)/(3x + 2) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 5)/(3x + 2) * (3x + 1)/(2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 4)(2x + 3)/(3x + 5)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(2x + 3)/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(2x + 3)/(3x + 2) * (3x + 2)/(3x + 1)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 3)(3x + 2)/(3x + 2)(3x + 1)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get (2x + 3)/(3x + 1) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 3)/(3x + 2) / (3x + 1)/(3x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 4)(2x + 3)/(3x + 5)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(2x + 5)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)*(2x + 5)/(2x + 1)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 1)(2x + 5)/(3x + 4)(2x + 1)\n\n2x + 1 cancels out, so we get (2x + 5)/(3x + 4) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 1)/(3x + 4) / (2x + 1)/(2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 4)(2x + 3)/(3x + 5)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(3x + 1)/(3x + 2)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 1)/(3x + 2) * (3x + 2)/(3x + 2)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 1)(3x + 2)/(3x + 2)(3x + 2)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get (3x + 1)/(3x + 2) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 1)/(3x + 2) / (3x + 2)/(3x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 5)(3x + 5)/(3x + 4)(3x + 2)"], "answer": "(6x^2 + 25x + 25)/(9x^2 + 18x + 8)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(2x + 5)/(3x + 4) * (3x + 5)/(3x + 2)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 5)(3x + 5)/(3x + 4)(3x + 2)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 5)/(3x + 4) / (3x + 2)/(3x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 5)(3x + 5)/(3x + 4)(3x + 2)"], "answer": "(3x + 2)/(2x + 3)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 2)(3x + 1)/(3x + 1)(2x + 3)\n\n3x + 1 cancels out, so we get (3x + 2)/(2x + 3) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 2)/(3x + 1) * (3x + 1)/(2x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 5)(3x + 5)/(3x + 4)(3x + 2)"], "answer": "(3x + 4)/(3x + 5)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 4)(2x + 3)/(2x + 3)(3x + 5)\n\n2x + 3 cancels out, so we get (3x + 4)/(3x + 5) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 4)/(2x + 3) * (2x + 3)/(3x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 5)(3x + 5)/(3x + 4)(3x + 2)"], "answer": "(2x + 3)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 5)/(3x + 4)*(2x + 3)/(3x + 5)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 5)(2x + 3)/(3x + 4)(3x + 5)\n\n3x + 5 cancels out, so we get (2x + 3)/(3x + 4) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 5)/(3x + 4) / (3x + 5)/(2x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 5)(3x + 5)/(3x + 4)(3x + 2)"], "answer": "(2x + 5)/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 4)/(2x + 1)*(2x + 5)/(3x + 4)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 4)(2x + 5)/(2x + 1)(3x + 4)\n\n3x + 4 cancels out, so we get (2x + 5)/(2x + 1) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 4)/(2x + 1) / (3x + 4)/(2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 5)(3x + 5)/(3x + 4)(3x + 2)"], "answer": "(3x + 5)/(2x + 3)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 5)/(2x + 3) * (2x + 3)/(2x + 3)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 5)(2x + 3)/(2x + 3)(2x + 3)\n\n2x + 3 cancels out, so we get (3x + 5)/(2x + 3) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 5)/(2x + 3) / (2x + 3)/(2x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 5)(3x + 5)/(3x + 4)(3x + 2)"], "answer": "(3x + 5)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 3)(3x + 5)/(3x + 4)(2x + 3)\n\n2x + 3 cancels out, so we get (3x + 5)/(3x + 4) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 3)/(3x + 4) * (3x + 5)/(2x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 5)(3x + 5)/(3x + 2)(2x + 3)"], "answer": "(9x^2 + 30x + 25)/(6x^2 + 13x + 6)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 5)/(3x + 2) * (3x + 5)/(2x + 3)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 5)(3x + 5)/(3x + 2)(2x + 3)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 5)/(3x + 2) / (2x + 3)/(3x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 5)(3x + 5)/(3x + 2)(2x + 3)"], "answer": "(2x + 5)/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 5)(2x + 5)/(2x + 1)(3x + 5)\n\n3x + 5 cancels out, so we get (2x + 5)/(2x + 1) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 5)/(2x + 1) * (2x + 5)/(3x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(2x + 3)/(2x + 1)(3x + 5)"], "answer": "(6x^2 + 11x + 3)/(6x^2 + 13x + 5)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 1)/(2x + 1) * (2x + 3)/(3x + 5)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 1)(2x + 3)/(2x + 1)(3x + 5)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 1)/(2x + 1) / (3x + 5)/(2x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(2x + 3)/(2x + 1)(3x + 5)"], "answer": "(3x + 4)/(3x + 2)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 4)/(2x + 5) * (2x + 5)/(3x + 2)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 4)(2x + 5)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)\n\n2x + 5 cancels out, so we get (3x + 4)/(3x + 2) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 4)/(2x + 5) / (3x + 2)/(2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 5)(3x + 2)/(2x + 1)(2x + 3)"], "answer": "(6x^2 + 19x + 10)/(4x^2 + 8x + 3)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 5)(3x + 2)/(2x + 1)(2x + 3)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 5)/(2x + 1) * (3x + 2)/(2x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 5)(3x + 2)/(2x + 1)(2x + 3)"], "answer": "(2x + 5)/(3x + 5)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 1)(2x + 5)/(3x + 5)(2x + 1)\n\n2x + 1 cancels out, so we get (2x + 5)/(3x + 5) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 1)/(3x + 5) * (2x + 5)/(2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 4)/(3x + 2)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(6x^2 + 11x + 4)/(9x^2 + 9x + 2)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(2x + 1)/(3x + 2) * (3x + 4)/(3x + 1)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 1)(3x + 4)/(3x + 2)(3x + 1)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 1)/(3x + 2) / (3x + 1)/(3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 4)/(3x + 2)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(2x + 5)/(2x + 3)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 5)/(2x + 3)*(2x + 5)/(3x + 5)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 5)(2x + 5)/(2x + 3)(3x + 5)\n\n3x + 5 cancels out, so we get (2x + 5)/(2x + 3) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 5)/(2x + 3) / (3x + 5)/(2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 4)/(3x + 2)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(2x + 3)/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(2x + 3)/(3x + 5) * (3x + 5)/(3x + 1)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 3)(3x + 5)/(3x + 5)(3x + 1)\n\n3x + 5 cancels out, so we get (2x + 3)/(3x + 1) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 3)/(3x + 5) / (3x + 1)/(3x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 3)(3x + 4)/(2x + 1)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(6x^2 + 17x + 12)/(6x^2 + 5x + 1)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 3)(3x + 4)/(2x + 1)(3x + 1)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 3)/(2x + 1) * (3x + 4)/(3x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 3)(3x + 4)/(2x + 1)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(3x + 2)/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 5)(3x + 2)/(3x + 1)(2x + 5)\n\n2x + 5 cancels out, so we get (3x + 2)/(3x + 1) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 5)/(3x + 1) * (3x + 2)/(2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 3)(3x + 4)/(2x + 1)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(3x + 4)/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 1)(3x + 4)/(3x + 1)(2x + 1)\n\n2x + 1 cancels out, so we get (3x + 4)/(3x + 1) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 1)/(3x + 1) * (3x + 4)/(2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 3)(3x + 4)/(2x + 1)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(3x + 1)/(3x + 2)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 1)(3x + 4)/(3x + 4)(3x + 2)\n\n3x + 4 cancels out, so we get (3x + 1)/(3x + 2) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 1)/(3x + 4) * (3x + 4)/(3x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 3)(3x + 4)/(2x + 1)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(2x + 1)/(3x + 2)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 1)(3x + 4)/(3x + 4)(3x + 2)\n\n3x + 4 cancels out, so we get (2x + 1)/(3x + 2) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 1)/(3x + 4) * (3x + 4)/(3x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 3)(3x + 4)/(2x + 1)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(3x + 5)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 5)/(2x + 5)*(3x + 5)/(3x + 5)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 5)(3x + 5)/(2x + 5)(3x + 5)\n\n3x + 5 cancels out, so we get (3x + 5)/(2x + 5) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 5)/(2x + 5) / (3x + 5)/(3x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 3)(3x + 4)/(2x + 1)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(2x + 5)/(3x + 2)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(2x + 5)/(3x + 2) * (3x + 2)/(3x + 2)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 5)(3x + 2)/(3x + 2)(3x + 2)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get (2x + 5)/(3x + 2) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 5)/(3x + 2) / (3x + 2)/(3x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 3)(3x + 4)/(2x + 1)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(2x + 5)/(3x + 5)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 5)(2x + 1)/(2x + 1)(3x + 5)\n\n2x + 1 cancels out, so we get (2x + 5)/(3x + 5) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 5)/(2x + 1) * (2x + 1)/(3x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 3)(3x + 4)/(2x + 1)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(3x + 4)/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 1)(3x + 4)/(2x + 1)(3x + 1)\n\n3x + 1 cancels out, so we get (3x + 4)/(2x + 1) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 1)/(2x + 1) * (3x + 4)/(3x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 3)(3x + 4)/(2x + 1)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(3x + 5)/(2x + 3)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(2x + 5)/(2x + 3)*(3x + 5)/(2x + 5)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 5)(3x + 5)/(2x + 3)(2x + 5)\n\n2x + 5 cancels out, so we get (3x + 5)/(2x + 3) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 5)/(2x + 3) / (2x + 5)/(3x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 3)(3x + 4)/(2x + 1)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(3x + 4)/(3x + 2)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 3)(3x + 4)/(3x + 2)(2x + 3)\n\n2x + 3 cancels out, so we get (3x + 4)/(3x + 2) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 3)/(3x + 2) * (3x + 4)/(2x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 2)(3x + 1)/(3x + 4)(2x + 3)"], "answer": "(9x^2 + 9x + 2)/(6x^2 + 17x + 12)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 2)(3x + 1)/(3x + 4)(2x + 3)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 2)/(3x + 4) * (3x + 1)/(2x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 2)(3x + 1)/(3x + 4)(2x + 3)"], "answer": "(3x + 4)/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 1)/(2x + 1)*(3x + 4)/(3x + 1)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 1)(3x + 4)/(2x + 1)(3x + 1)\n\n3x + 1 cancels out, so we get (3x + 4)/(2x + 1) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 1)/(2x + 1) / (3x + 1)/(3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 2)(3x + 1)/(3x + 4)(2x + 3)"], "answer": "(3x + 2)/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 2)/(2x + 1) * (2x + 1)/(3x + 1)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 2)(2x + 1)/(2x + 1)(3x + 1)\n\n2x + 1 cancels out, so we get (3x + 2)/(3x + 1) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 2)/(2x + 1) / (3x + 1)/(2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 2)(3x + 1)/(3x + 4)(2x + 3)"], "answer": "(3x + 2)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 2)/(3x + 5) * (3x + 5)/(2x + 5)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 2)(3x + 5)/(3x + 5)(2x + 5)\n\n3x + 5 cancels out, so we get (3x + 2)/(2x + 5) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 2)/(3x + 5) / (2x + 5)/(3x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 2)(3x + 1)/(3x + 4)(2x + 3)"], "answer": "(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(2x + 3)/(3x + 4)*(2x + 1)/(2x + 3)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 3)(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)(2x + 3)\n\n2x + 3 cancels out, so we get (2x + 1)/(3x + 4) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 3)/(3x + 4) / (2x + 3)/(2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 2)(2x + 3)/(3x + 5)(3x + 4)"], "answer": "(6x^2 + 13x + 6)/(9x^2 + 27x + 20)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 2)/(3x + 5) * (2x + 3)/(3x + 4)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 2)(2x + 3)/(3x + 5)(3x + 4)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 2)/(3x + 5) / (3x + 4)/(2x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 2)(2x + 3)/(3x + 5)(3x + 4)"], "answer": "(3x + 1)/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 1)/(3x + 5) * (3x + 5)/(2x + 1)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 1)(3x + 5)/(3x + 5)(2x + 1)\n\n3x + 5 cancels out, so we get (3x + 1)/(2x + 1) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 1)/(3x + 5) / (2x + 1)/(3x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 2)(2x + 3)/(3x + 5)(3x + 4)"], "answer": "(2x + 3)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 2)/(2x + 5)*(2x + 3)/(3x + 2)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 2)(2x + 3)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get (2x + 3)/(2x + 5) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 2)/(2x + 5) / (3x + 2)/(2x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 2)(2x + 3)/(3x + 5)(3x + 4)"], "answer": "(2x + 1)/(3x + 5)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 1)/(3x + 5)*(2x + 1)/(3x + 1)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 1)(2x + 1)/(3x + 5)(3x + 1)\n\n3x + 1 cancels out, so we get (2x + 1)/(3x + 5) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 1)/(3x + 5) / (3x + 1)/(2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 2)(2x + 3)/(3x + 5)(3x + 4)"], "answer": "(3x + 5)/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 5)/(2x + 5) * (2x + 5)/(2x + 1)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 5)(2x + 5)/(2x + 5)(2x + 1)\n\n2x + 5 cancels out, so we get (3x + 5)/(2x + 1) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 5)/(2x + 5) / (2x + 1)/(2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 2)(2x + 3)/(3x + 5)(3x + 4)"], "answer": "(2x + 5)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 5)(2x + 1)/(2x + 1)(3x + 4)\n\n2x + 1 cancels out, so we get (2x + 5)/(3x + 4) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 5)/(2x + 1) * (2x + 1)/(3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 3)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 4)"], "answer": "(6x^2 + 11x + 3)/(6x^2 + 23x + 20)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 3)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 4)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 3)/(2x + 5) * (3x + 1)/(3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 3)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 4)"], "answer": "(3x + 5)/(2x + 3)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 5)/(2x + 3) * (2x + 3)/(2x + 3)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 5)(2x + 3)/(2x + 3)(2x + 3)\n\n2x + 3 cancels out, so we get (3x + 5)/(2x + 3) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 5)/(2x + 3) / (2x + 3)/(2x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 3)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 4)"], "answer": "(3x + 5)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 2)(3x + 5)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get (3x + 5)/(2x + 5) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 2)/(2x + 5) * (3x + 5)/(3x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 3)(3x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 4)"], "answer": "(3x + 4)/(2x + 3)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(2x + 1)/(2x + 3)*(3x + 4)/(2x + 1)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 1)(3x + 4)/(2x + 3)(2x + 1)\n\n2x + 1 cancels out, so we get (3x + 4)/(2x + 3) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 1)/(2x + 3) / (2x + 1)/(3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(3x + 5)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)"], "answer": "(9x^2 + 18x + 5)/(6x^2 + 19x + 10)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 1)/(2x + 5) * (3x + 5)/(3x + 2)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 1)(3x + 5)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 1)/(2x + 5) / (3x + 2)/(3x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 3)(3x + 4)/(3x + 2)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(6x^2 + 17x + 12)/(9x^2 + 9x + 2)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(2x + 3)/(3x + 2) * (3x + 4)/(3x + 1)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 3)(3x + 4)/(3x + 2)(3x + 1)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 3)/(3x + 2) / (3x + 1)/(3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 3)(3x + 4)/(3x + 2)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 2)(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)(3x + 2)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get (2x + 1)/(3x + 4) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 2)/(3x + 4) * (2x + 1)/(3x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 5)(3x + 1)/(2x + 3)(2x + 1)"], "answer": "(9x^2 + 18x + 5)/(4x^2 + 8x + 3)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 5)/(2x + 3) * (3x + 1)/(2x + 1)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 5)(3x + 1)/(2x + 3)(2x + 1)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 5)/(2x + 3) / (2x + 1)/(3x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 5)(3x + 1)/(2x + 3)(2x + 1)"], "answer": "(2x + 1)/(3x + 5)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 1)(3x + 2)/(3x + 2)(3x + 5)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get (2x + 1)/(3x + 5) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 1)/(3x + 2) * (3x + 2)/(3x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(2x + 5)/(2x + 3)(2x + 3)"], "answer": "(6x^2 + 17x + 5)/(4x^2 + 12x + 9)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 1)(2x + 5)/(2x + 3)(2x + 3)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 1)/(2x + 3) * (2x + 5)/(2x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(2x + 5)/(2x + 3)(2x + 3)"], "answer": "(3x + 5)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 5)/(2x + 1) * (2x + 1)/(2x + 5)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 5)(2x + 1)/(2x + 1)(2x + 5)\n\n2x + 1 cancels out, so we get (3x + 5)/(2x + 5) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 5)/(2x + 1) / (2x + 5)/(2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(2x + 5)/(2x + 3)(2x + 3)"], "answer": "(3x + 5)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 5)/(2x + 1) * (2x + 1)/(3x + 4)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 5)(2x + 1)/(2x + 1)(3x + 4)\n\n2x + 1 cancels out, so we get (3x + 5)/(3x + 4) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 5)/(2x + 1) / (3x + 4)/(2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(3x + 5)(3x + 4)"], "answer": "(6x^2 + 5x + 1)/(9x^2 + 27x + 20)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(3x + 5)(3x + 4)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 1)/(3x + 5) * (3x + 1)/(3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(3x + 5)(3x + 4)"], "answer": "(3x + 5)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(2x + 5)/(3x + 4)*(3x + 5)/(2x + 5)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 5)(3x + 5)/(3x + 4)(2x + 5)\n\n2x + 5 cancels out, so we get (3x + 5)/(3x + 4) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 5)/(3x + 4) / (2x + 5)/(3x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(3x + 5)(3x + 4)"], "answer": "(3x + 4)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 4)/(2x + 1) * (2x + 1)/(2x + 5)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 4)(2x + 1)/(2x + 1)(2x + 5)\n\n2x + 1 cancels out, so we get (3x + 4)/(2x + 5) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 4)/(2x + 1) / (2x + 5)/(2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(3x + 5)(3x + 4)"], "answer": "(3x + 5)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 5)/(3x + 4) * (3x + 4)/(3x + 4)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 5)(3x + 4)/(3x + 4)(3x + 4)\n\n3x + 4 cancels out, so we get (3x + 5)/(3x + 4) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 5)/(3x + 4) / (3x + 4)/(3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(3x + 5)(3x + 4)"], "answer": "(2x + 3)/(3x + 5)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(2x + 3)/(2x + 1) * (2x + 1)/(3x + 5)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 3)(2x + 1)/(2x + 1)(3x + 5)\n\n2x + 1 cancels out, so we get (2x + 3)/(3x + 5) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 3)/(2x + 1) / (3x + 5)/(2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(3x + 5)(3x + 4)"], "answer": "(3x + 1)/(2x + 3)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 1)/(2x + 5) * (2x + 5)/(2x + 3)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 1)(2x + 5)/(2x + 5)(2x + 3)\n\n2x + 5 cancels out, so we get (3x + 1)/(2x + 3) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 1)/(2x + 5) / (2x + 3)/(2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(3x + 5)(3x + 4)"], "answer": "(3x + 5)/(2x + 3)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 5)(2x + 1)/(2x + 1)(2x + 3)\n\n2x + 1 cancels out, so we get (3x + 5)/(2x + 3) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 5)/(2x + 1) * (2x + 1)/(2x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(3x + 5)(3x + 4)"], "answer": "(3x + 4)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 2)(3x + 4)/(2x + 5)(3x + 2)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get (3x + 4)/(2x + 5) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 2)/(2x + 5) * (3x + 4)/(3x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(3x + 5)(3x + 4)"], "answer": "(2x + 3)/(3x + 2)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 4)/(3x + 2)*(2x + 3)/(3x + 4)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 4)(2x + 3)/(3x + 2)(3x + 4)\n\n3x + 4 cancels out, so we get (2x + 3)/(3x + 2) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 4)/(3x + 2) / (3x + 4)/(2x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 1)/(3x + 5)(3x + 4)"], "answer": "(3x + 2)/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 2)/(3x + 1) * (3x + 1)/(3x + 1)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 2)(3x + 1)/(3x + 1)(3x + 1)\n\n3x + 1 cancels out, so we get (3x + 2)/(3x + 1) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 2)/(3x + 1) / (3x + 1)/(3x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 5)(2x + 3)/(3x + 2)(2x + 5)"], "answer": "(6x^2 + 19x + 15)/(6x^2 + 19x + 10)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 5)(2x + 3)/(3x + 2)(2x + 5)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 5)/(3x + 2) * (2x + 3)/(2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(2x + 5)/(3x + 2)(3x + 4)"], "answer": "(6x^2 + 17x + 5)/(9x^2 + 18x + 8)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 1)(2x + 5)/(3x + 2)(3x + 4)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 1)/(3x + 2) * (2x + 5)/(3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(2x + 5)/(3x + 2)(3x + 4)"], "answer": "(2x + 3)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 3)(3x + 2)/(3x + 2)(3x + 4)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get (2x + 3)/(3x + 4) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 3)/(3x + 2) * (3x + 2)/(3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(2x + 5)/(3x + 2)(3x + 4)"], "answer": "(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(2x + 1)/(2x + 5) * (2x + 5)/(3x + 4)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 1)(2x + 5)/(2x + 5)(3x + 4)\n\n2x + 5 cancels out, so we get (2x + 1)/(3x + 4) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 1)/(2x + 5) / (3x + 4)/(2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(2x + 5)/(3x + 2)(3x + 4)"], "answer": "(2x + 5)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(2x + 5)/(3x + 4) * (3x + 4)/(3x + 4)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 5)(3x + 4)/(3x + 4)(3x + 4)\n\n3x + 4 cancels out, so we get (2x + 5)/(3x + 4) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 5)/(3x + 4) / (3x + 4)/(3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(2x + 5)/(3x + 2)(3x + 4)"], "answer": "(3x + 2)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 2)/(2x + 5) * (2x + 5)/(2x + 5)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 2)(2x + 5)/(2x + 5)(2x + 5)\n\n2x + 5 cancels out, so we get (3x + 2)/(2x + 5) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 2)/(2x + 5) / (2x + 5)/(2x + 5)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 4)(3x + 2)/(3x + 5)(2x + 3)"], "answer": "(9x^2 + 18x + 8)/(6x^2 + 19x + 15)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 4)/(3x + 5) * (3x + 2)/(2x + 3)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 4)(3x + 2)/(3x + 5)(2x + 3)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 4)/(3x + 5) / (2x + 3)/(3x + 2)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 4)/(3x + 1)(3x + 5)"], "answer": "(6x^2 + 11x + 4)/(9x^2 + 18x + 5)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(2x + 1)/(3x + 1) * (3x + 4)/(3x + 5)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 1)(3x + 4)/(3x + 1)(3x + 5)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 1)/(3x + 1) / (3x + 5)/(3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(2x + 1)(3x + 4)/(3x + 1)(3x + 5)"], "answer": "(2x + 3)/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 3)(3x + 4)/(3x + 4)(2x + 1)\n\n3x + 4 cancels out, so we get (2x + 3)/(2x + 1) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 3)/(3x + 4) * (3x + 4)/(2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 4)(3x + 1)/(2x + 3)(2x + 3)"], "answer": "(9x^2 + 15x + 4)/(4x^2 + 12x + 9)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 4)/(2x + 3) * (3x + 1)/(2x + 3)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 4)(3x + 1)/(2x + 3)(2x + 3)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 4)/(2x + 3) / (2x + 3)/(3x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 4)(3x + 1)/(2x + 3)(2x + 3)"], "answer": "(3x + 5)/(2x + 1)", "explanation": "We can make this problem simpler by turning it into a multiplication problem.\n Multiply the first rational expression by the reciprocal of the second, so that the expression becomes this:\n(3x + 5)/(2x + 1) * (2x + 1)/(2x + 1)\n\nNow we can solve it like a multiplication problem. Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 5)(2x + 1)/(2x + 1)(2x + 1)\n\n2x + 1 cancels out, so we get (3x + 5)/(2x + 1) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 5)/(2x + 1) / (2x + 1)/(2x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 4)(3x + 5)/(3x + 2)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(9x^2 + 27x + 20)/(9x^2 + 9x + 2)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 4)(3x + 5)/(3x + 2)(3x + 1)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 4)/(3x + 2) * (3x + 5)/(3x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 4)(3x + 5)/(3x + 2)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 1)(2x + 3)/(2x + 3)(3x + 4)\n\n2x + 3 cancels out, so we get (2x + 1)/(3x + 4) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 1)/(2x + 3) * (2x + 3)/(3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 4)(3x + 5)/(3x + 2)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(3x + 4)/(3x + 1)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 4)(3x + 2)/(3x + 2)(3x + 1)\n\n3x + 2 cancels out, so we get (3x + 4)/(3x + 1) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 4)/(3x + 2) * (3x + 2)/(3x + 1)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 4)(3x + 5)/(3x + 2)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(2x + 1)/(2x + 3)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 1)(2x + 5)/(2x + 5)(2x + 3)\n\n2x + 5 cancels out, so we get (2x + 1)/(2x + 3) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 1)/(2x + 5) * (2x + 5)/(2x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 4)(3x + 5)/(3x + 2)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 1)(3x + 5)/(3x + 5)(3x + 4)\n\n3x + 5 cancels out, so we get (2x + 1)/(3x + 4) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 1)/(3x + 5) * (3x + 5)/(3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 4)(3x + 5)/(3x + 2)(3x + 1)"], "answer": "(3x + 5)/(3x + 2)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(2x + 3)(3x + 5)/(3x + 2)(2x + 3)\n\n2x + 3 cancels out, so we get (3x + 5)/(3x + 2) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(2x + 3)/(3x + 2) * (3x + 5)/(2x + 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)(3x + 4)"], "answer": "(6x^2 + 5x + 1)/(9x^2 + 24x + 16)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 1)(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)(3x + 4)\n\nSince we can\u0027t simplify this expression anymore by canceling like terms, we can leave the answer like this or multiply the factors together.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 1)/(3x + 4) * (2x + 1)/(3x + 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"alternatives": ["(3x + 1)(2x + 1)/(3x + 4)(3x + 4)"], "answer": "(2x + 1)/(2x + 5)", "explanation": "Multiply the numerators together and the denominators together:\n(3x + 4)(2x + 1)/(2x + 5)(3x + 4)\n\n3x + 4 cancels out, so we get (2x + 1)/(2x + 5) as the answer.", "question": "Simplify:\n(3x + 4)/(2x + 5) * (2x + 1)/(3x + 4)", "type": "text"}
]}